You saw the hottie. yeah?
Do you mean
the E-Rank? I sure did!
His body is ridiculous.
He has an average face. but he
does kinda lean toward cute.
Guy looks scrawny till he takes
his shirt off. then it's like. oh. damn.
When did we admit
a patient as ripped as that?
Not ringing any bells for me.
He didn't really
stand out much at first.
apparently he started exercising.
though. and it did his body good.
There's no way. Takes more than
a couple of days to build up muscle.
Excuse me. Mister Jinwoo Sung...
Huh? I'm sorry.
No. my fault entirely.
so. please. don't be!
His muscles... are incredible!
Was he always this hot?
I mean. surely he was. right?
Do you...
need something from me?
Oh. yes!
I just came to see how you're feeling
since you're being discharged today.
I'm honestly feeling pretty good.
That's wonderful.
Stop by reception whenever you're ready
and we'll get your paperwork filed. okay?
Sure. Thank you for everything.
-Oh. and...
-What?
If it's all right. may I have your
phone number before you go?
You want my phone number?
Yes... long as you
don't mind. of course.
Must have a test result or
two they still need to send me.
Yeah. that's not a problem.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hello. and good morning. everyone!
Joining us today.
we have a very special guest.
I'm Yoonho Baek and I run
the White Tiger Guild.
As one of just seven S-Rank
hunters in the entire country.
I imagine your schedule stays pretty
full. so I appreciate you fitting us in.
Apart from talk show
appearances and gate exploration.
what exactly is a hunter's life like?
Busy. for sure. There's
lots of training involved.
Hunters are gifted.
but far from perfect.
Getting out of touch with the feel
of combat can dull our instincts.
no matter how enhanced they are.
So you train every day?
That must be exhausting.
In my case. no. Before I became
a hunter I was a firefighter.
so staying in good shape
was just routine.
My comrades' lives are at stake. Not
being at my best could mean the worst.
That thought alone
keeps me on my toes.
That's some motivation.
-The White Tiger Guild...
-Oh. crap. is that the time?
Hey. Jinwoo?
G'morning. Jinah.
Oh what? You're already up.
Been awake a while now.
Have fun at school.
There are leftovers from last night's
dinner in the fridge. if you're hungry.
Okay so. have you been working out?
Uh... yeah. a little.
You also look a lot taller.
which is weird.
Abs. I can understand. but height?
It's kinda cool! I guess that
even guys in their 20s can grow!
I'll see ya later.
Hey. hey...
don't forget an umbrella.
No. that's heavy and it's so nice out.
Yeah. look up the word "heavy"
when you get to class.
Aw. gimme a break.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
All right!
Gee. thanks. Bye. pushy!
Be careful out there.
I'll save the running for later.
Man. I really am jacked.
Talk about a stat boost.
Bet I could become a bodybuilder
if I keep investing points in strength.
Speaking of. I've got
some points to divvy up.
But where. that is the question.
Strength raises the damage I can do.
But that's pretty useless
if I can't land any hits.
Agility should help with that.
I'll definitely increase those two.
Can't go wrong with vitality either.
Perception has come in handy.
but intellect...
seems magic related.
so do I really need it?
Okay. I've got it.
That looks good.
Huh?
Oh. Hello. Jinwoo Sung speaking!
You finally picked up.
I'm so sorry. been stuck
in the hospital. sir.
I take it you're calling
to ask about the rent. right?
Right. Still waiting on
this month's payment.
But I can push it back
if money's tight.
N-No need!
I'll send it right away!
Oh. I'll keep an eye out. then.
You take care of yourself.
now. young man.
I will. thank you. sir.
I don't know if this change I'm going
through is a re-awakening or what.
But. now that I'm able to slay
goblins without almost dying.
making rent shouldn't be too hard.
That said. it won't
exactly be easy either.
Bottom line. if I wanna earn good money.
I have to go through higher ranked gates.
Trouble with that is no sane person'll let
an E-Rank hunter just cruise into those.
Maybe I'll get reevaluated.
A higher rank could let me
access better gates
and make some extra cash
just from the publicity.
Uh. might get
too much publicity. though.
Re-awakenings
are newsworthy as it is.
But a hunter who can level up
and get stronger by the day?
That's unheard of.
I can practically see the headlines.
All eyes would be on me.
And the nail that sticks out
gets hammered down.
No.
I think it'd be for the best
to keep my secret to myself.
At least. until I have
a solid grasp on this power.
Confirm.
Hey. there!
-The name's Dongsuk Hwang.
-And mine's Jinwoo Sung.
-E-Rank. right?
-Yes. sir.
Oh. hey. you're him! The dude
that's. like. known for being horrible.
If memory serves. you're called
"The Weakest Hunter of All Mankind."
-Are you serious!
-That's enough out of both of you.
So much for starting
things off on the right foot.
No. it's fine. E-Ranks can be
laughably bad. Will that be an issue?
Not as far as I'm concerned.
We need you to meet the quota. and
that's more important than your rank.
I told you over the phone. but
you're mainly here for the headcount
since we need a minimum of eight
hunters to enter a C-Rank dungeon.
Half the party has to be C-Rank.
too. but we've got that covered.
You aren't gonna be fighting in there. so we
won't be sharing any of the spoils with you.
You'll still get your two million
for participating. though.
Not bad. eh?
Four C-Ranks and two sub-D-Ranks.
Not bad at all. Just tell me
what I have to do. sir.
You'll be in charge
of hauling our bags.
They've got food. spare clothing. gear.
first aid kit's somewhere in there. too.
First aid? There isn't
a healer on this squad?
Independent parties like ours
have a hard time
retaining healers.
as I'm sure you can imagine.
We do all our raids without
a healer. so we're used to it.
Huh.
A strike squad with nothing
but tanks and damage dealers.
Are they crazy?
Going in without a healer
really bugs me.
Just sign on the dotted line.
and we can be on our way.
"I recognize the party is not liable for
anything that occurs inside the dungeon."
Sure.
-Here.
-Thank ya.
Hello there.
fellow temporary recruit!
My name's Jinho Yoo.
I'm a 21-year-old D-Rank hunter. and I
signed up as a quota guy. just like you!
I see.
A D-Rank with that gear?
Is this kid a trust fund baby?
It's your first C-Rank raid ever?
Huh! Don't you worry.
I'll be there to keep you safe!
Awesome.
Let's move out!
Those bags look really heavy.
think that you'll be okay?
Yes. but. thank you.
Oh. come on. bro. I'm younger than you. so
just drop all the "please" and "thank-yous."
Works for me.
Did you hear about the president of
the firm who was handling this site?
He fled overseas two months ago
with the 900 billion he embezzled.
while the workers and investors
were left holding the bag.
Ahh. Just look at me rambling
without reading the mood again.
For some strange reason. I've never been
great at picking up on social cues. ever.
Here we are.
Damn! That is one huge. swirly light!
Don't see gates this big very often.
We really don't. which makes me
feel like it should be ranked higher.
You know what I mean. boss?
The Association folks said it was
a C gate after checking it twice.
and they're pretty thorough
about that stuff.
C-Rank or not. a gate with its
own postal code seems bad. right?
The size of the gate doesn't
really tell us anything.
The magic power within it is what
counts so I think we'll be just fine.
When Mister Hwang said. "they checked it".
he meant they measured its magic.
We wouldn't even be allowed
to raid it if it were B or higher.
larger guilds handle
the more dangerous dungeons.
Hm. your brain's kinda
blowing mine away. Jinwoo.
I may be an E-Rank. but I
have been doing this awhile.
Don't get cocky.
It's still your first C-Rank raid.
Okay. follow me. we're goin' in!
Yes. sir!
Steel yourself. and let's go!
Yeah. right behind you.
Huh!
Hey. Gyu-hwan. a little light?
Sure.
Well. this is different.
no beasts to greet us?
Awfully dark for a dungeon. too.
Yeah. where are the glow stones
in the walls that light the way?
A pitch-black dungeon.
Reminds me of the Cartenon Temple.
Hey. quick question. What
did he mean by "glow stones?"
Oh... they're shiny rocks.
It's common to find them all over the
ground and walls of cave-like dungeons.
They give off this faint light
that illuminates the area.
I wouldn't mind
having a few right now.
So. an essence stone is the kind
you recover from a magic beast.
a mana stone is what you can
mine from the dungeon itself.
and then there's a glow stone that has
a more practical use of lighting caves.
Seems easy to mix them up.
You'll get the hang of it soon enough.
What if it's a bust? Just a big.
empty cave. What d'you think?
Could a dungeon without a
single magic beast even exist?
Quiet.
I hear them. they found us.
They just haven't
shown themselves yet.
Everyone ready?
What moves as a group. lives in the dark.
but is drawn to light when they sense it?
We're dealing with insect-types!
-Insects?
-Damn it. no wonder it's dark!
-What do you see over there. boss?
-Buncha nothin'. they're hiding!
Don't tell me it's an ant colony!
Great. now you went and jinxed us!
The sound's getting closer!
Where the hell are they?
Too many tunnels to choose!
There!
-Kyuhwan!
-On it!
-I'll draw their attention away!
-Right!
Stick with me. Jinwoo.
I'll keep you safe from these things!
What are you waiting for. huh?
Come get me!
He got every creepy crawly
to head straight for him!
A taunt skill. no wonder he's C-Rank.
Hey. on your left. Jinsuk!
Yeah. I got 'em!
-I'll help!
-No. just stay back!
I'm counting down!
Five. four. three. two. one. zero!
Have a piece of this!
Very nice. now. finish it!
Aw. hell. yeah!
Nice chemistry. they've obviously
been working together for a long time.
Still. since they operate without a
healer. they're a little too aggressive.
And Jinho. his fancy gear
makes up for his lack of skill.
Everyone's doing fine. I guess.
But...
something feels off.
That the last one? Well?
Yeah. that was all of 'em.
-We're done here. you guys.
-Then it's looting time!
Gather up the essence stones
and divide the lot by seven!
Yes. sir!
This is my favorite part of the job.
Same.
That was some call you made. Jinwoo.
Those bugs about ambushed us.
Glad to help.
How were you able to tell they
were attacking us from above?
-Instinct.
-Huh.
Then your instincts are
very sharp. We'd be dead!
Hey. boss. get a load of this!
The wounds on these bugs.
No weapon of ours made those.
Exactly. And they're not
burns from magic. either.
I'm not sure what did this.
but they weren't just killed.
these suckers were torn apart.
Maybe they had a turf battle
with some other magic beasts.
Which implies that there's
a more dominant creature
than these freaks crawling
around in here somewhere.
Huh...
What could be big enough
to prey on these.
That was amazing!
Like. did you see me slash
that one bug down the middle?
Yeah.
So your sword. and all of your
armor. bet they weren't cheap.
Uhh. you're right.
they were a gift from my dad.
He wanted to honor
my first raid and all.
Well. just make sure
to watch your back.
I get the sense we'll need to.
Six. seven. Eight. nine. and... ten!
Whoa! Did a bomb just
go off in our building?
Settle down. that's
a standard occurrence here.
It's just the Guildmaster training.
That much damage from one hit?
Damn.
Well. that didn't get me
anywhere near warmed up.
Hey. can I get
a clean-up crew in here?
We there yet?
-The size of a dungeon has nothing to--
-Nothing to do with its rank. right?
I was listening when you
talked about magic power ratings.
Does that mean this dungeon
is vast but mostly empty?
Sure does.
Dude. it must be hard lugging
around all that stuff in this huge place.
Really. bro.
I don't mind helping you.
They're really not
as heavy as you would think.
I'm also getting paid without fighting
magic beasts. which is a pretty sweet deal.
Or at least I thought it was.
Now. it seems too sweet.
What's this nagging feeling?
We're a battle-tested party.
without a healer.
And they needed extra members.
Another half-dead one.
-Nice!
-Thanks.
Something's up with this place.
We've covered a ton of ground. but none
of the beasts we've come across are healthy.
Every insect since that first
swarm has been injured or dead.
There's a boss in here
somewhere. there's gotta be.
A gate wouldn't have
opened if there wasn't.
Hang on. Kyuhwan.
light the way ahead.
Sure.
This path definitely
leads to the boss chamber.
Stay alert!
-Jackpot!
-No way.
Look at all of these mana crystals!
They're just so beautiful!
They aren't worth as much as
essence stones. but this haul?
It's gotta be worth billions.
if not more!
Y'know. Boss. I bet even your brother
would be jealous of a find like this!
Dude! Shut up! Why did you have to
bring up the boss' brother. huh? Not cool!
Dongsoo. what'd I tell you?
You don't always get
to be the one who's right.
Better not expect your big
brother to bow down to you now.
'Cause this score is just the thing
to make my strike team blow up!
Once we split this seven ways. no doubt
it's gonna be over a 100 million each!
But how are we gonna carry it all?
Hey. Jinwoo. can I see the contract that
you signed before entering the dungeon?
There's something I wanna
double-check for you.
Okay.
Excuse me. Mister Hwang. sir?
According to Jinwoo's contract.
he should be in on this.
Battle drops are the only
things he doesn't get a share of.
Since mana crystals are excavated
as opposed to being dropped by beasts.
shouldn't this particular find be
split eight ways instead of seven?
Well. of course.
let's split it all evenly!
Fair is fair. after all.
But first...
There's some
company we should see to.
The dungeon boss!
In case you didn't know. rookie. the
gate will close once that thing dies.
Mining and carrying out
this truckload of crystals
comes before exterminating
the colossal spider.
Fortunately. it seems to be asleep. which
gives us the perfect chance to excavate.
So. where's the gear?
I mean. I wasn't expecting there to
be a treasure trove of mana crystals.
I left all of the transport and
mining tools back with my ride.
Chul-jin. don't I always say
be prepared for anything?
-I'm really sorry.
-Guess it can't be helped now.
Why don't you two stay here
for a bit and protect our prize.
-We'll go get the mining equipment.
-Wh... Stay here?
This is the boss' lair.
we have the lowest ranks!
You'll be just fine.
That thing looks like it's
sound asleep on a full stomach.
I doubt anything could snap it
awake unless you did it intentionally.
Even so!
This is your first raid. yet
you think you know better?
Jinwoo's in the same boat since
this is his first C-Rank dungeon.
Have a little faith. will ya?
Take a break.
Actually. I need a break
with my team. too.
Got lots to discuss.
Regulations say you need eight
members to take on a C-Rank dungeon.
Their squad only consists of six.
We do all our raids without
a healer. so we're used to it.
"Used to it".
suggests they've taken on
a fair share of C-Rank dungeons
before this one.
So why recruit Jinho and me instead
of having regular temps on call?
All right...
go ahead and seal off the
entrance to the lair. Kyuhwan.
No! No!
Considering the timing.
I think they just betrayed us.
I knew it. those bastards.
In a hunter's line of work.
you run into some real crooks.
Our job will always have some risk.
mistakes and accidents are bound to happen.
But since those accidents
occur inside gates.
it's easy for anyone with
ill intent to commit a crime
and then never see
their offense come to light.
It's not like there are
surveillance cameras in there.
And without living witnesses
there's zero evidence.
Sometimes weak people
get used as bait
to lure out the magic beasts.
or they get left behind.
Cast aside.
The way lizards lose their tails.
They're really trying to kill us.
All because they want
more lousy mana crystals?
If I...
If I hadn't brought up that stupid
contract. then maybe we'd...
No. we were in their trap.
They were ready to strike us down
on the spot after one wrong move.
More importantly.
Jinwoo. I said I would protect
you. so that's what I'll do!
Somehow. I'll manage!
We could get out
from there if we needed.
But I bet they thought of that too.
A C-Rank boss. an E-Rank hunter.
This thing's on a whole other level.
Other level?
No.
I take that back.
Jinho. don't move.
I'm gonna fight this thing.
Wait. you mean like fight-fight?
I mean this one's mine.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm